Are you ready to gaze into hell?
The Accursed is a horror film directed by Kevin Lewis.
Elly is asked by a family friend to spend a few days looking
after an elderly woman living in a remote cabin.
She readily agrees thinking a short trip to the woods will be a nice escape.
The cabin turns out to be anything but relaxing as Elly begins
hallucinating in ways that blur reality with her dreams.
As the visions take over, Elly realizes that she was lured there by a demonic
presence hiding inside of the woman just waiting to break free.
Elly, played by Sarah Grey.
Ms. Ambrose, played by Meg Foster.
Beth, played by Sarah Dumont.
Mary Lynn, played by Alexis Knapp.
Alma, played by Mena Suvari.
Officer Green, played by Sherman Augustus.
Malekith the Accursed () is a fictional character appearing in
American comic books published by Marvel Comics.
He is the ruler of the Dark Elves of Svartalfheim
and has come into conflict with Thor.
Malekith has often wielded the Casket of Ancient Winters, which
enables him to generate endless amounts of ice.
Christopher Eccleston portrayed the character in the Marvel
Cinematic Universe film Thor: The Dark World (2013).
Additionally, Quinton Flynn and James C.
Mathis III voiced Malekith in guest appearances in The Avengers: Earth's
Mightiest Heroes and Hulk and the Agents of S.M.A.S.H.
respectively.
The film explores themes of dreams, cabin, demon.
The tone is dark.